rootofgood.com 2019-06-22

# Privacy - Root of Good

## PRIVACY POLICY

Our goal is to respect your privacy and not do anything unexpected with any personal information you may provide.  If you leave a comment and it says your email will not be displayed, that is the truth.  I will see it as a site administrator, but no one else will.

### Information that is gathered from visitors

In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor’s IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.Where registration is required, the visitor’s email and a username will be stored on the server.

### How the Information is used

The information is used to enhance the vistor’s experience when using the website to display personalised content and possibly advertising.E-mail addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to 3rd parties. 

E-mail may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers by us or our affiliates.

### **Visitor Options**

If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in e-mail that you receive.  [Contact me ](https://rootofgood.com/contact/ "Contact")if you keep getting emails from Root of Good.   **I hate spam as much as you do, and I will figure out why the system likes emailing you so much.**

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website.

### **Cookies**

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. Also they may be used to track your return visits to the website.

3rd party advertising companies may also use cookies for tracking purposes.

### Third Party Use of Personal information

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

### Display Ads

The Website may use third party advertising networks to manage all third-party advertising on the Website. These third party networks serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies. Third party networks may collect IP addresses and location to serve personalized ads.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Additional Information on Root of Good [Affiliate Relationships and Affiliate Links](https://rootofgood.com/affiliate-disclaimer/).

Additional information on [Root of Good Terms of Use](https://rootofgood.com/terms-of-use/).

* * *

**Root of Good Recommends:**

  * [Personal Capital](https://rootofgood.com/personalcapital)* - It's the best FREE way to track your spending, income, and entire investment portfolio all in one place. Did I mention it's FREE?
  * [Free Travel](https://rootofgood.com/go/travelcreditcard)* - We score $10,000 worth of free travel every year from credit card sign up bonuses. Get your free travel, too.
  * Save more on travel with [Airbnb and take $40 off your first stay](https://rootofgood.com/airbnb)*. We usually get apartments with 2-3 bedrooms plus a kitchen and living room for less than the price of 1 hotel room. Save even more with weekly and monthly discounts.
  * Use a shopping portal like [Ebates](https://rootofgood.com/go/ebates)* and save more on everything you buy online. [Get a $10 bonus](https://rootofgood.com/go/ebates)* when you sign up now.
  * $20 off [Uber](https://rootofgood.com/go/uber)* and [Lyft](https://rootofgood.com/lyft20)* for new customers (our preferred rideshare apps when traveling)
  * [Google Fi](https://rootofgood.com/go/googlefi)* - Use the link and save $20 on unlimited calls and texts for US cell service plus 200+ countries of free international coverage. Only $20 per month plus $10 per GB data.

* Affiliate links. If you click on a link and do business with these companies, we may earn a small commission. 

* * *
